Guide to the Bob Fitch Photography Archive M1994
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 7: Negatives, 1964-2004
  - Fitch 371-375 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Fitch 376-380 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Fitch 381-385 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Fitch 386-390 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Fitch 391-395 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Fitch 396-400 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Fitch 401-405 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Fitch 406-410 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Fitch 411-415 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Fitch 416-420 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Fitch 421-425 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 82, Folder 15)
    423 removed to Series 2: Classics.
  - Fitch 426-430 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Fitch 431-435 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Fitch 436-440 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Fitch 441-445 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - Fitch 446-450 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - Fitch 451-455 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Fitch 456-460 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    456 missing or omitted.
  - Fitch 461-465 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Fitch 466-470 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Fitch 471-475 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Fitch 476-480 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Fitch 481-485 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Fitch 486-490 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Fitch 491-495 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Fitch 496-500 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Fitch 501-505 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Fitch 506-510 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Fitch 511-515 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Fitch 516-520 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Fitch 521-525 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Fitch 526-530 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Fitch 531-535 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Fitch 536-540 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Fitch 541-545 [negatives], 1966-1967 (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Fitch 546-550 [negatives], 1967 (Box 83, Folder 19)
    548 missing or omitted.
  - Fitch 551-555 [negatives], 1967 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Fitch 556-560 [negatives], 1967 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Fitch 561-565 [negatives], 1967 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Fitch 566-570 [negatives], 1967 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Fitch 571-575 [negatives], 1967 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Fitch 576-580 [negatives], 1967 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Fitch 581-585 [negatives], 1967 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Fitch 586-590 [negatives], 1967 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    586 missing or omitted.
  - Fitch 591-595 [negatives], 1967 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Fitch 596-600 [negatives], 1967 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Fitch 601-605 [negatives], 1967 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Fitch 606-610 [negatives], 1967 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Fitch 611-615 [negatives], 1967 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Fitch 616-620 [negatives], 1967 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - Fitch 621-625 [negatives], 1967 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Fitch 626-630 [negatives], 1967 (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - Fitch 631-635 [negatives], 1967 (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - Fitch 636-640 [negatives], 1967 (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - Fitch 641-645 [negatives], 1967 (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - Fitch 646-650 [negatives], 1967 (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - Fitch 651-655 [negatives], 1967 (Box 84, Folder 21)
  - Fitch 656-660 [negatives], 1967 (Box 84, Folder 22)
  - Fitch 661-665 [negatives], 1967 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Fitch 666-670 [negatives], 1967 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Fitch 671-675 [negatives], 1967 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Fitch 676-680 [negatives], 1967 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Fitch 681-685 [negatives], 1967 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Fitch 686-690 [negatives], 1967 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Fitch 691-695 [negatives], 1967 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Fitch 696-700 [negatives], 1967 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Fitch 701-705 [negatives], 1967 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Fitch 706-710 [negatives], 1967 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Fitch 711-715 [negatives], 1967 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Fitch 716-720 [negatives], 1967 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Fitch 721-725 [negatives], 1967 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    725 removed to Series 2: Classics.
  - Fitch 726-730 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Fitch 731-735 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Fitch 736-740 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Fitch 741-745 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - Fitch 746-750 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - Fitch 751-755 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - Fitch 756-760 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - Fitch 761-765 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 85, Folder 21)
  - Fitch 766-770 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 85, Folder 22)
  - Fitch 771-775 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Fitch 776-780 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Fitch 781-785 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Fitch 786-790 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Fitch 791-795 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Fitch 796-800 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Fitch 801-805 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Fitch 806-810 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Fitch 811-815 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Fitch 816-820 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Fitch 821-825 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Fitch 826-830 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Fitch 831-835 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Fitch 836-840 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Fitch 841-845 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Fitch 846-850 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - Fitch 851-855 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Fitch 856-860 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 86, Folder 18)
    856 and 857 missing or omitted.
  - Fitch 861-865 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - Fitch 866-870 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 86, Folder 20)
  - Fitch 871-875 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Fitch 876-880 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Fitch 881-885 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Fitch 886-890 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Fitch 891-895 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Fitch 896-900 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Fitch 901-905 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Fitch 906-910 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Fitch 911-915 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Fitch 916-920 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Fitch 921-925 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 87, Folder 11)
    922 missing.
  - Fitch 926-930 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Fitch 931-935 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Fitch 936-940 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Fitch 941-945 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Fitch 946-950 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Fitch 951-955 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - Fitch 956-960 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - Fitch 961-965 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 87, Folder 19)
  - Fitch 966-970 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 87, Folder 20)
  - Fitch 971-975 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 87, Folder 21)
  - Fitch 976-980 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Fitch 981-985 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Fitch 986-990 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Fitch 991-995 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    994 removed to Series 2: Classics.
  - Fitch 996-1000 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Fitch 1001-1005 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Fitch 1006-1010 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Fitch 1011-1015 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Fitch 1016-1020 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Fitch 1021-1025 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Fitch 1026-1030 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Fitch 1031-1035 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Fitch 1036-1040 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Fitch 1041-1045 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Fitch 1046-1050 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Fitch 1051-1055 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Fitch 1056-1060 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 88, Folder 17)
  - Fitch 1061-1065 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 88, Folder 18)
  - Fitch 1066-1070 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 88, Folder 19)
  - Fitch 1071-1075 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 88, Folder 20)
  - Fitch 1076-1080 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 88, Folder 21)
  - Fitch 1081-1085 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Fitch 1086-1090 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Fitch 1091-1095 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Fitch 1096-1100 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Fitch 1101-1105 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Fitch 1106-1110 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Fitch 1111-1115 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Fitch 1116-1120 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Fitch 1121-1125 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Fitch 1126-1130 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    1128 missing.
  - Fitch 1131-1135 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Fitch 1136-1140 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - Fitch 1141-1145 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - Fitch 1146-1150 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - Fitch 1151-1155 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - Fitch 1156-1160 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - Fitch 1161-1165 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 89, Folder 17)
  - Fitch 1166-1170 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 89, Folder 18)
  - Fitch 1171-1175 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 89, Folder 19)
    1173, 1174 and 1175 missing negatives.
  - Fitch 1176-1180 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 89, Folder 20)
  - Fitch 1181-1185 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 89, Folder 21)
  - Fitch 1186-1190 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 89, Folder 22)
  - Fitch 1191-1195 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Fitch 1196-1200 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Fitch 1201-1205 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Fitch 1206-1210 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Fitch 1211-1215 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Fitch 1216-1220 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Fitch 1221-1225 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Fitch 1226-1230 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Fitch 1231-1235 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Fitch 1236-1240 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Fitch 1241-1245 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Fitch 1246-1250 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Fitch 1251-1255 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Fitch 1256-1260 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Fitch 1261-1265 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - Fitch 1266-1270 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - Fitch 1271-1275 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - Fitch 1276-1280 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 90, Folder 18)
  - Fitch 1281-1285 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 90, Folder 19)
    1285 removed to Series 2: Classics.
  - Fitch 1286-1290 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 90, Folder 20)
    1286 missing.
  - Fitch 1291-1295 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 90, Folder 21)
  - Fitch 1296-1300 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 90, Folder 22)
  - Fitch 1301-1305 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Fitch 1306-1310 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Fitch 1311-1315 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Fitch 1316-1320 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Fitch 1321-1325 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Fitch 1326-1330 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Fitch 1331-1335 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    1333 removed to Series 2: Classics.
  - Fitch 1336-1340 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Fitch 1341-1345 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Fitch 1346-1350 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Fitch 1351-1355 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Fitch 1356-1360 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Fitch 1361-1365 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Fitch 1366-1370 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 91, Folder 14)
    1369 missing.
  - Fitch 1371-1375 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - Fitch 1376-1380 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - Fitch 1381-1385 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - Fitch 1386-1390 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - Fitch 1391-1395 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - Fitch 1396-1400 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 91, Folder 20)
  - Fitch 1401-1405 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 91, Folder 21)
    1402 removed to Series 2: Classics. 1403 missing or omitted.
  - Fitch 1406-1410 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 91, Folder 22)
  - Fitch 1411-1415 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 91, Folder 23)
    1414 removed to Series 2: Classics.
  - Fitch 1416-1420 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    1416 removed to Series 2: Classics.
  - Fitch 1421-1425 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Fitch 1426-1430 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    1430 removed to Series 2: Classics.
  - Fitch 1431-1435 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Fitch 1436-1440 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    1437 removed to Series 2: Classics.
  - Fitch 1441-1445 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Fitch 1446-1450 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Fitch 1451-1455 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Fitch 1456-1460 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Fitch 1461-1465 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Fitch 1466-1470 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    1469 missing.
  - Fitch 1471-1475 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Fitch 1476-1480 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Fitch 1481-1485 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Fitch 1486-1490 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Fitch 1491-1495 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - Fitch 1496-1500 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - Fitch 1501-1505 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 92, Folder 18)
  - Fitch 1506-1510 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 92, Folder 19)
  - Fitch 1511-1515 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 92, Folder 20)
  - Fitch 1516-1520 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 92, Folder 21)
  - Fitch 1521-1525 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 92, Folder 22)
  - Fitch 1526-1530 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 92, Folder 23)
  - Fitch 1531-1535 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Fitch 1536-1540 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Fitch 1541-1545 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Fitch 1546-1550 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Fitch 1551-1555 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Fitch 1556-1560 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    1556 removed. 1557, 1558 and 1559 missing or omitted.
  - Fitch 1561-1565 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    1562-1565 removed [per Bob Fitch note].
  - Fitch 1566-1570 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    1566 and 1567 removed [per Bob Fitch note].
  - Fitch 1571-1575 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Fitch 1576-1580 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    1578-1580 missing or omitted.
  - Fitch 1581-1595 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    1581-1593 missing or omitted.
  - Fitch 1596-1600 [negatives], 1967-1970 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Fitch 1601-1605 [negatives], 1970 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Fitch 1606-1610 [negatives], 1970 (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - Fitch 1611-1615 [negatives], 1970 (Box 93, Folder 15)
    1613 and 1614 removed.
  - Fitch 1616-1620 [negatives], 1970 (Box 93, Folder 16)
    1620 removed.
  - Fitch 1621-1625 [negatives], 1970 (Box 93, Folder 17)
    1621, 1622 and 1624 removed.
  - Fitch 1626-1630 [negatives], 1970 (Box 93, Folder 18)
    1628 removed.
  - Fitch 1631-1650 [negatives], 1970 (Box 93, Folder 19)
    1632, 1634-1650 removed.
  - Fitch 1651-1655 [negatives], 1970 (Box 93, Folder 20)
    1651 and 1652 removed.
  - Fitch 1656-1660 [negatives], 1970 (Box 93, Folder 21)
    1659 removed.
  - Fitch 1661-1665 [negatives], 1970 (Box 93, Folder 22)
  - Fitch 1666-1670 [negatives], 1970 (Box 93, Folder 23)
    1670 removed.
  - Fitch 1671-1685 [negatives], 1970 (Box 93, Folder 24)
    1671-1681 removed.
  - Fitch 1686-1690 [negatives], 1970 (Box 93, Folder 25)
  - Fitch 1691-1695 [negatives], 1970 (Box 93, Folder 26)
    1692 removed.
  - Fitch 1696-1700 [negatives], 1970 (Box 93, Folder 27)
  - Fitch 1701-1705 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Fitch 1706-1710 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Fitch 1711-1715 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Fitch 1716-1720 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Fitch 1721-1725 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Fitch 1726-1730 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    1727 removed.
  - Fitch 1731-1735 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Fitch 1736-1740 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    1737-1740 removed.
  - Fitch 1741-1745 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Fitch 1746-1750 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    1747-1749 removed.
  - Fitch 1751-1760 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    1753-1755 removed. 1756-1760 missing or omitted.
  - Fitch 1761-1765 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    1761-1763 missing or omitted. 1765 removed.
  - Fitch 1766-1770 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 13)
    1766-1770 removed.
  - Fitch 1771-1775 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 14)
    1771, 1773-1775 removed.
  - Fitch 1776-1780 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 15)
    1776, 1777 and 1780 removed.
  - Fitch 1781-1795 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 16)
    1781-1792 and 1794 removed.
  - Fitch 1796-1800 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 17)
    1800 removed.
  - Fitch 1801-1810 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 18)
    1801-1805 removed.
  - Fitch 1811-1815 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Fitch 1816-1820 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 20)
    1818-1820 removed.
  - Fitch 1821-1835 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 21)
    1821-1834 removed.
  - Fitch 1836-1840 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 22)
  - Fitch 1841-1845 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 23)
    1844 missing or omitted.
  - Fitch 1846-1850 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 24)
  - Fitch 1851-1855 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 25)
  - Fitch 1856-1860 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 26)
  - Fitch 1861-1865 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 27)
    1862-1865 removed.
  - Fitch 1866-1870 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 28)
    1866 and 1868 removed. 1867 missing or omitted.
  - Fitch 1871-1880 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 29)
    1875-1880 removed.
  - Fitch 1881-1885 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 30)
  - Fitch 1886-1890 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 31)
  - Fitch 1891-1895 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 32)
  - Fitch 1896-1900 [negatives], 1970 (Box 94, Folder 33)
    1898 removed.
  - Fitch 1901-1915 [negatives], 1970 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    1901, 1904-1913 removed.
  - Fitch 1916-1920 [negatives], 1970 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    1919 and 1917 removed.
  - Fitch 1921-1925 [negatives], 1970 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    1924 removed. 1925 missing.
  - Fitch 1926-1930 [negatives], 1970 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    1926, 1927 and 1930 removed. 1928 missing.
  - Fitch 1931-1935 [negatives], 1970 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    1932, 1933 and 1935 removed.
  - Fitch 1936-1940 [negatives], 1970 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    1938-1940 removed.
  - Fitch 1941-1945 [negatives], 1970 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    1942-1944 removed.
  - Fitch 1946-1950 [negatives], 1970 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    1946 and 1948 removed.
  - Fitch 1951-1955 [negatives], 1970 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Fitch 1956-1960 [negatives], 1970 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    1956 removed. 1957-1959 missing or omitted.
  - Fitch 1961-1965 [negatives], 1970 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    1962-1964 removed.
  - Fitch 1966-1970 [negatives] (Box 95, Folder 12)
    1966 removed.
  - Fitch 1971-2010 [negatives], 1970 (Box 95, Folder 13)
    1975-2007 removed.
  - Fitch 2011-2015 [negatives], 1970 (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - Fitch 2016-2020 [negatives], 1970 (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - Fitch 2021-2025 [negatives], 1970 (Box 95, Folder 16)
    2023 missing or omitted.
  - Fitch 2026-2030 [negatives], 1970 (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - Fitch 2031-2035 [negatives], 1970 (Box 95, Folder 18)
  - Fitch 2036-2040 [negatives], 1970 (Box 95, Folder 19)
  - Fitch 2041-2045 [negatives], 1970 (Box 95, Folder 20)
  - Fitch 2046-2050 [negatives], 1970 (Box 95, Folder 21)
    2050 missing or omitted.
  - Fitch 2051-2055 [negatives], 1970 (Box 95, Folder 22)
  - Fitch 2056-2060 [negatives], 1970 (Box 95, Folder 23)
  - Fitch 2061-2065 [negatives], 1970 (Box 95, Folder 24)
  - Fitch 2066-2070 [negatives], 1970 (Box 95, Folder 25)
  - Fitch 2071-2075 [negatives], 1970 (Box 95, Folder 26)
    2075-2077 removed. 2078-2080 missing or omitted.
  - Fitch 2081-2100 [negatives], 1970 (Box 95, Folder 27)
    2081, 2083-2097 removed.
  - Fitch 2101-2105 [negatives], 1970 (Box 95, Folder 28)
    2102 removed to Series 2: Classics. 2104 missing or omitted.
  - Fitch 2106-2110 [negatives], 1970 (Box 95, Folder 29)
  - Fitch 2111-2115 [negatives], 1970 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Fitch 2116-2120 [negatives], 1970 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    2119 and 2120 removed.
  - Fitch 2121-2140 [negatives], 1970 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    2123-2139 removed.
  - Fitch 2141-2145 [negatives], 1970 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    2141-2143 removed.
  - Fitch 2146-2150 [negatives], 1970 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Fitch 2151-2155 [negatives], 1970 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    2154 removed.
  - Fitch 2156-2160 [negatives], 1970 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Fitch 2161-2165 [negatives], 1970 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Fitch 2166-2175 [negatives], 1970 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    2168-2174 removed.
  - Fitch 2176-2180 [negatives], 1970 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    2176, 2178 and 2179 removed.
  - Fitch 2181-2185 [negatives], 1970 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    2181-2184 removed.
  - Fitch 2186-2190 [negatives], 1970 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    2186 removed.
  - Fitch 2191-2195 [negatives], 1970 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Fitch 2196-2200 [negatives], 1970 (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - Fitch 2201-2205 [negatives], 1970 (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - Fitch 2206-2210 [negatives], 1970 (Box 96, Folder 16)
  - Fitch 2211-2215 [negatives], 1970 (Box 96, Folder 17)
  - Fitch 2216-2220 [negatives], 1970 (Box 96, Folder 18)
  - Fitch 2221-2135 [negatives], 1970 (Box 96, Folder 19)
    2222-2233 removed.
  - Fitch 2236-2240 [negatives], 1970 (Box 96, Folder 20)
  - Fitch 2241-2245 [negatives], 1970 (Box 96, Folder 21)
  - Fitch 2246-2250 [negatives], 1970 (Box 96, Folder 22)
  - Fitch 2251-2255 [negatives], 1970 (Box 96, Folder 23)
  - Fitch 2256-2260 [negatives], 1970 (Box 96, Folder 24)
  - Fitch 2261-2265 [negatives], 1970 (Box 96, Folder 25)
  - Fitch 2266-2270 [negatives], 1970 (Box 96, Folder 26)
  - Fitch 2271-2275 [negatives], 1970 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Fitch 2276-2280 [negatives], 1970 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Fitch 2281-2285 [negatives], 1970 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Fitch 2286-2290 [negatives], 1970 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    2290 removed.
  - Fitch 2291-2295 [negatives], 1970 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    2291 removed.
  - Fitch 2296-2300 [negatives], 1970 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Fitch 2301-2305 [negatives], 1970 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Fitch 2306-2310 [negatives], 1970 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Fitch 2311-2315 [negatives], 1970 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Fitch 2316-2320 [negatives], 1970 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Fitch 2321-2325 [negatives], 1970 (Box 97, Folder 11)